{
"2025-01-01": {"answers":"january","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: for fathers and long days.","q2":"5th: for mothers and Jedi.","q3":"4th: for bunnies and pranks.","q4":"3rd: for pies and madness.","q5":"2nd: for love and leaps."},
"2025-01-02": {"answers":"alien,aliens,extraterrestrial being,e.t.,e.t. the extra terrestrial,e.t. the extra-terrestrial","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm not from here.","q2":"I might not speak your language.","q3":"I‚Äôm out of this world.","q4":"Many claim to have seen me, but no one has proof.","q5":"I might have landed in a UFO."},
"2025-01-03": {"answers":"carrot,carrots","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You can make a cake with me.","q2":"Change my first letter to ‚Äòp‚Äô and I become a bird.","q3":"Snowmen love me.","q4":"Bunnies love me.","q5":"I‚Äôm an orange root vegetable."},
"2025-01-04": {"answers":"eiffel tower,the eiffel tower","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I have one apartment.","q2":"I‚Äôm made of iron.","q3":"I look like an A.","q4":"This isn‚Äôt me:üóº","q5":"I‚Äôm an iconic Paris structure."},
"2025-01-05": {"answers":"glass","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm molten and cooled rock.","q2":"A me is made out of me. Mes used to be made out of me.","q3":"Without me, you can‚Äôt play riddl.ing on your phone.","q4":"If you‚Äôre inside, you need me to look outside.","q5":"A magnifying me is also made out of me."},
"2025-01-06": {"answers":"panda,pandas,giant panda,panda bear","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm alive.","q2":"I‚Äôm black.","q3":"I‚Äôm white.","q4":"I‚Äôm furry.","q5":"I love eating bamboo."},
"2025-01-07": {"answers":"register","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm a list of entries.","q2":"I‚Äôm a musical range.","q3":"My bell rings when I open.","q4":"Do me to sign up.","q5":"I‚Äôm a book of births and deaths; a style of language or instrument; a cash or memory store; what you do to make an account.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-01-08": {"answers":"bed,bedroom","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm here every day.","q2":"I often don‚Äôt see anything here.","q3":"I might be on a queen.","q4":"I‚Äôm lying down.","q5":"My head is on a pillow."},
"2025-01-09": {"answers":"toilet,toilets","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You use me every day.","q2":"Some use me in one way and some use me in two ways.","q3":"A dog‚Äôs version of me is outside.","q4":"Wash your hands after using me.","q5":"Flush me after using me."},
"2025-01-10": {"answers":"underwear,undergarment","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You usually don‚Äôt want others to see me.","q2":"I go on first and off last.","q3":"I‚Äôm often washed.","q4":"I fit you.","q5":"Other clothes are worn over me."},
"2025-01-11": {"answers":"question,questions","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"There‚Äôs one of me right now.","q2":"Do me to a suspect.","q3":"Play a game with twenty of me.","q4":"I‚Äôm asked.","q5":"I come before an answer."},
"2025-01-12": {"answers":"anthem,national anthem","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You probably know one of me.","q2":"I‚Äôm different depending on where you live.","q3":"Some of me are multilingual.","q4":"I‚Äôm sung...","q5":"...especially in schools or before sports."},
"2025-01-13": {"answers":"seoul","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"There‚Äôs a wide river here.","q2":"The name of this place means ‚Äúcapital‚Äù.","q3":"I have really fast internet here.","q4":"I‚Äôm at the heart and soul of e-sports.","q5":"I‚Äôm in the capital of K-wave.","message":"Guest riddle by kylli"},
"2025-01-14": {"answers":"fan,fans","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I follow.","q2":"I blow.","q3":"My mail contains gifts, my fiction is unofficial, and my service is catering.","q4":"I‚Äôll cool you down or cheer you up.","q5":"I support my favourites or I circulate air.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-01-15": {"answers":"thesaurus","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôll help you write.","q2":"I‚Äôm not a dinosaur...","q3":"...nor antediluvian; extinct; fossil; pass√©; relic; out-of-date; unfashionable.","q4":"I‚Äôm full of synonyms.","q5":"I‚Äôm a dictionary of similar words."},
"2025-01-16": {"answers":"ant,ants","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I live in hills.","q2":"I‚Äôm rarely lonely.","q3":"A fire me might hurt you.","q4":"I like to march with my army.","q5":"I‚Äôm a colonial insect."},
"2025-01-17": {"answers":"mystery,murder mystery","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm solved.","q2":"I might feature cases.","q3":"If you don‚Äôt know the answer, it might be a me.","q4":"I might feature detectives.","q5":"I‚Äôm a crime genre."},
"2025-01-18": {"answers":"hunt","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Cats do me.","q2":"I might be illegal, depending on what you do me to.","q3":"I can be done to treasure, game, and witches.","q4":"You might use weapons for doing me.","q5":"I‚Äôm what predators do to prey."},
"2025-01-19": {"answers":"cheese,cheeses","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm catupiry or sulguni.","q2":"I‚Äôm kashkaval or rubing.","q3":"I‚Äôm brunost or cottage.","q4":"I‚Äôm swiss or feta.","q5":"I‚Äôm mozzarella or brie."},
"2025-01-20": {"answers":"gulp","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"‚ÄúUh oh!‚Äù","q2":"You might do me when you‚Äôre scared.","q3":"You might do me down to something unappetizing.","q4":"You might do me for air after a long dive underwater.","q5":"I‚Äôm the sound of a nervous swallow."},
"2025-01-21": {"answers":"plug","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I go into walls.","q2":"Pull me after your bath.","q3":"Now, here‚Äôs a me for our sponsor!","q4":"I look different in different countries.","q5":"I connect to sockets, stop holes from draining, and advertise products.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-01-22": {"answers":"russia,russian federation","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: has kangaroos and vegemite.","q2":"5th: has capybaras and feijoada.","q3":"4th: has eagles and cheeseburgers.","q4":"3rd: has pandas and wontons.","q5":"2nd: has beavers and poutine."},
"2025-01-23": {"answers":"marshmallow","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm popular at camps.","q2":"I‚Äôm easily burnt.","q3":"I‚Äôm usually white.","q4":"I contain gelatin.","q5":"I‚Äôm a sweet squishy foam."},
"2025-01-24": {"answers":"flag,flags","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I wave.","q2":"I‚Äôm black and white if you‚Äôre about to stop.","q3":"I‚Äôm white if you want to stop.","q4":"Seeing me might tell you where someone‚Äôs from.","q5":"I‚Äôm fabric on a pole."},
"2025-01-25": {"answers":"blind","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Take a me guess.","q2":"Love is me.","q3":"You have me spots.","q4":"You read with your fingers if you‚Äôre me.","q5":"I‚Äôm the inability to see."},
"2025-01-26": {"answers":"vine,vines,grapevine,ivy,climber","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I climb walls.","q2":"I grow up.","q3":"I make walls green.","q4":"My name comes from wine.","q5":"A grape me grows grapes."},
"2025-01-27": {"answers":"moment","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm fleeting.","q2":"Drumrolls, please... the me of truth!","q3":"Hold or hang on a me.","q4":"Take a photo to capture a me.","q5":"I‚Äôm a single point in time."},
"2025-01-28": {"answers":"dragon,dragons,chinese dragon","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm long.","q2":"I have two or four legs (depending on where I‚Äôm from).","q3":"It‚Äôs my year.","q4":"I‚Äôm a mystical, flying, rain-making serpent.","q5":"I‚Äôm a winged fire-breathing lizard.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-01-29": {"answers":"snake,snakes","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I can kill you.","q2":"I represent good and evil, health, rebirth, and eternity.","q3":"I eat animals whole.","q4":"I lose my skin.","q5":"I‚Äôm a slithering serpent."},
"2025-01-30": {"answers":"bean,beans","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm vanilla.","q2":"I‚Äôm jelly.","q3":"I‚Äôm kidney.","q4":"I‚Äôm soy.","q5":"I‚Äôm coffee."},
"2025-01-31": {"answers":"sticker","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm one-sided.","q2":"I‚Äôm peeled.","q3":"I might say ‚Äú4011‚Äù on a banana.","q4":"I might tell you something‚Äôs origin or discount.","q5":"I‚Äôm sticky."},
"2025-02-01": {"answers":"tail,tails","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You don‚Äôt have me.","q2":"Some coats, some hairstyles, and some letters have me.","q3":"Comets, coins, and planes have me.","q4":"Kites and dragons have me.","q5":"Cats and dogs have me, while apes and frogs don‚Äôt."},
"2025-02-02": {"answers":"cold","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I can be an excuse to stay home.","q2":"People use a powered box to keep things me.","q3":"If you stay in the me, you might catch a me.","q4":"Put on some clothes if it‚Äôs me.","q5":"I‚Äôm not hot."},
"2025-02-03": {"answers":"museum,museums,art museum,science museum,natural history museum,louvre,art gallery,exhibition","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"I should be quiet here.","q2":"I shouldn‚Äôt run here.","q3":"There are things I shouldn‚Äôt touch here.","q4":"I bought a ticket to come here.","q5":"There are artworks and exhibits here."},
"2025-02-04": {"answers":"script,scripts","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You can read me.","q2":"I‚Äôm a small program.","q3":"Post me: I forgot to tell you something.","q4":"Super me to raise to a power.","q5":"I‚Äôm a movie‚Äôs lines.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-02-05": {"answers":"bone,bones","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You have me.","q2":"Spiders don‚Äôt have me.","q3":"People take me out of fish.","q4":"Dogs love me.","q5":"I‚Äôm made of calcium and collagen."},
"2025-02-06": {"answers":"life vest,life jacket,lifejacket,lifebuoy,personal flotation device","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm coloured brightly...","q2":"...so you‚Äôre easy to spot.","q3":"I can save your life.","q4":"I‚Äôm found under the seats of certain vehicles.","q5":"I inflate and float."},
"2025-02-07": {"answers":"cyclone,hurricane,typhoon,tropical storm,tropical cyclone,tropical depression,waterspout,extratropical cyclone","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I grow in water.","q2":"I shrink on land.","q3":"It‚Äôs calm in my centre...","q4":"...but the rest of me brings disaster.","q5":"I‚Äôm a spinning storm of wind and water."},
"2025-02-08": {"answers":"mural","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm seen by many people.","q2":"I can be made in seconds or years.","q3":"I might reduce vandalism.","q4":"Graffiti and fresco are forms of me.","q5":"I‚Äôm a painting on a wall."},
"2025-02-09": {"answers":"windmill,windmills,wind turbine","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm popular in the Netherlands.","q2":"I spin.","q3":"I‚Äôm originally used to process grain or pump water.","q4":"I have three or more sails.","q5":"I convert wind power to energy."},
"2025-02-10": {"answers":"plunger","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You hopefully don‚Äôt need me...","q2":"...but you should have me, just in case.","q3":"I‚Äôm used on bowls.","q4":"I create pressure by moving back and forth.","q5":"I‚Äôm a rubber toilet unclogger."},
"2025-02-11": {"answers":"trailer","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm pulled.","q2":"I tease.","q3":"I might have spoilers.","q4":"I follow tractors.","q5":"I come before a film or after a truck.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-02-12": {"answers":"lantern","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm carried or hung.","q2":"Some versions of me fly up.","q3":"I might be made of metal, paper, or pumpkin.","q4":"I use oil, wax, or electricity.","q5":"I‚Äôm an enclosed light source."},
"2025-02-13": {"answers":"earth","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: big and blue.","q2":"5th: cold and sideways.","q3":"4th: got a nice ring to it!","q4":"3rd: the largest with a great spot.","q5":"2nd: rocky, red, and rovered."},
"2025-02-14": {"answers":"cupid","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I‚Äôll shoot you...","q2":"...and it‚Äôll feel great.","q3":"I look like a child.","q4":"I use a bow.","q5":"I‚Äôll make you fall in love."},
"2025-02-15": {"answers":"battery","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm a store.","q2":"I make things portable.","q3":"You might get worried if I‚Äôm low.","q4":"I‚Äôm charged.","q5":"I power electronics."},
"2025-02-16": {"answers":"vomit,vomiting,puke,barf,throw up","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm gross.","q2":"If someone else does me, don‚Äôt get hit.","q3":"You usually don‚Äôt intend to do me...","q4":"...unless you ate something poisonous.","q5":"I‚Äôm an involuntary stomach purge."},
"2025-02-17": {"answers":"pigeon,dove,pigeons,doves,homing pigeons,pigeons and doves","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm common in cities.","q2":"I can carry messages.","q3":"I can carry diseases.","q4":"A white me represents peace.","q5":"I‚Äôm an everyday bird."},
"2025-02-18": {"answers":"crane,cranes","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I fly or build.","q2":"You can fold me with paper.","q3":"I lift heavy things.","q4":"A thousand of my origami are said to grant a wish.","q5":"I‚Äôm a long-legged bird or a tall construction machine.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-02-19": {"answers":"desert","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"Everything looks the same here.","q2":"Few people live here.","q3":"Animals here include lions, kangaroos, and snakes.","q4":"You might see mirages here.","q5":"It almost never rains here."},
"2025-02-20": {"answers":"dessert","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Examples of me include kaju katli, m√§mmi, and¬†pristi√±os.","q2":"There‚Äôs always room for me.","q3":"I‚Äôm a treat.","q4":"I‚Äôm rarely savoury.","q5":"I‚Äôm a sweet course at the end of a meal."},
"2025-02-21": {"answers":"roller coasters,rollercoaster,rollercoasters,roller coaster","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I go in circles.","q2":"I go up and down.","q3":"I make people scream.","q4":"You should be fastened to your seat.","q5":"I‚Äôm an amusement park thrill ride."},
"2025-02-22": {"answers":"helmet,riding helmet","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You can wear me.","q2":"I‚Äôll protect you.","q3":"I‚Äôm required at certain areas.","q4":"I‚Äôm required when riding certain vehicles.","q5":"I‚Äôm a hard head covering."},
"2025-02-23": {"answers":"lighter,cigarette lighter","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You may need me on a birthday.","q2":"I‚Äôm found in convenience stores.","q3":"I often use butane.","q4":"You may need me if you smoke.","q5":"I‚Äôm a portable fire-making device."},
"2025-02-24": {"answers":"gold","prompt":"What connects all five words?","q1":"1. Heart.","q2":"2. Rush.","q3":"3. Fool.","q4":"4. Mine.","q5":"5. Digger.","message":"Connections"},
"2025-02-25": {"answers":"chip,chips","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôve become smaller and faster over time.","q2":"I‚Äôm a short shot to the green.","q3":"You move all of me in.","q4":"I‚Äôm paired with fish.","q5":"I‚Äôm a byte-based circuit, a golf swing, a casino currency, or a bite-sized snack.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-02-26": {"answers":"mime,mimes","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I perform.","q2":"I often wear white makeup.","q3":"I‚Äôm silent.","q4":"I may seem stuck in an invisible box.","q5":"I act with facial expressions and body movements."},
"2025-02-27": {"answers":"waiter,waitress","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I bus.","q2":"I sound patient.","q3":"I serve.","q4":"I might expect tips.","q5":"I take orders and serve food."},
"2025-02-28": {"answers":"information,info","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"A group of soldiers might be me?","q2":"Ew, too much me!","q3":"An insider might have me you don‚Äôt.","q4":"A newspaper spreads me.","q5":"I‚Äôm part of IT."},
"2025-03-01": {"answers":"hydrogen","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: caesium.","q2":"5th: rubidium.","q3":"4th: potassium.","q4":"3rd: sodium.","q5":"2nd: lithium.","message":"Sixday"},
"2025-03-02": {"answers":"seven","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm the minimum moves to solve the three disk Towers of Hanoi.","q2":"I‚Äôm how many cervical vertebrae you have.","q3":"I‚Äôm the number of sharps in the key of C-sharp major.","q4":"I‚Äôm how many hills Rome was built on.","q5":"I‚Äôm the number of stars in the Big Dipper."},
"2025-03-03": {"answers":"cap,baseball cap","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I might show something you like.","q2":"I might be adjusted with elastic, velcro, or snaps.","q3":"I can be worn forwards and backwards.","q4":"My bill or brim blocks the sun from your eyes.","q5":"Traditionally, I display a baseball team‚Äôs logo."},
"2025-03-04": {"answers":"remote","prompt":"Where/what am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm far.","q2":"I make things louder or quieter.","q3":"Very few people are here.","q4":"I turn things on or off.","q5":"I‚Äôm a wireless controller or a distant place.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-03-05": {"answers":"yellow","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"My stone is a popular attraction.","q2":"My card means you did something wrong.","q3":"My light tells you to slow down.","q4":"I‚Äôm in the middle of Romania, Vietnam, and an egg.","q5":"I‚Äôm a sunny colour."},
"2025-03-06": {"answers":"puzzle","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm Rush Hour or Portal.","q2":"I‚Äôm a helpmate or tsumego.","q3":"I‚Äôm a nonogram or a sudoku.","q4":"I‚Äôm Tetris or a Rubik‚Äôs cube.","q5":"I‚Äôm a crossword or a jigsaw."},
"2025-03-07": {"answers":"aloe vera,aloe","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm invasive.","q2":"I‚Äôm evergreen.","q3":"I‚Äôm used in cosmetics.","q4":"I soothe burns.","q5":"I‚Äôm a succulent with thick leaves."},
"2025-03-08": {"answers":"giga","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: yotta.","q2":"5th: zetta.","q3":"4th: exa.","q4":"3rd: peta.","q5":"2nd: tera.","message":"Sixday"},
"2025-03-09": {"answers":"barbie","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I love fashion.","q2":"I have many professions.","q3":"Pink is my favourite colour.","q4":"I‚Äôm named after a young girl.","q5":"I‚Äôm a popular doll."},
"2025-03-10": {"answers":"matcha","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm bitter.","q2":"I‚Äôm solid and usually made into a liquid.","q3":"My name is Japanese.","q4":"I‚Äôm green.","q5":"I‚Äôm a flavourful ground tea."},
"2025-03-11": {"answers":"line","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I can be short or long.","q2":"I can be skipped or cut.","q3":"I‚Äôm straight in mathematics, but can be winding in real life.","q4":"Another name for me sounds like the letter ‚ÄòQ‚Äô.","q5":"I‚Äôm a connection from one point to another, or a bunch of waiting people.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-03-12": {"answers":"poland","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"There‚Äôs an art museum here.","q2":"There‚Äôs a soap museum here.","q3":"There‚Äôs a Holocaust museum here.","q4":"There‚Äôs a Chopin museum and a Marie Curie museum here.","q5":"There‚Äôs a film museum in ≈Å√≥d≈∫, a pinball museum in Krak√≥w, and a National Museum of Technology in Warsaw here."},
"2025-03-13": {"answers":"book","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You can scan me.","q2":"Change my first letter and you can use me to fish.","q3":"You can flip me.","q4":"You can read me.","q5":"I‚Äôm a collection of pages put together."},
"2025-03-14": {"answers":"death","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I can be peaceful or violent.","q2":"I may judge you.","q3":"I may wear a black robe.","q4":"I‚Äôm the end.","q5":"I may carry a sickle."},
"2025-03-15": {"answers":"mandarin chinese,mandarin,chinese","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: Bengali.","q2":"5th: Portuguese.","q3":"4th: Hindi.","q4":"3rd: English.","q5":"2nd: Spanish.","message":"Sixday"},
"2025-03-16": {"answers":"reverse","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You don‚Äôt want to eat in me.","q2":"Wearing something in me might be embarrassing.","q3":"A kayak and racecar stay the same in me.","q4":"A truck in me might beep.","q5":"!em ni m‚ÄòI"},
"2025-03-17": {"answers":"radio,radios","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm useful in the wilderness or in a zombie apocalypse.","q2":"I‚Äôm most popular in cars.","q3":"I‚Äôm tuned.","q4":"I‚Äôm a wireless receiver.","q5":"I‚Äôm like livestreamed podcasts."},
"2025-03-18": {"answers":"cloud,clouds","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm reachable through the Internet.","q2":"I‚Äôm made of water.","q3":"You can use me to store files.","q4":"I‚Äôm in the sky.","q5":"I‚Äôm an online storage provider or a suspension of water drops.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-03-19": {"answers":"gym,gymnasium","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"There are bars here.","q2":"There are balls here.","q3":"There are mills here.","q4":"There are bikes here.","q5":"There are weights here."},
"2025-03-20": {"answers":"dye,dyes,pigment,pigments","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I can be made of petroleum.","q2":"I can be applied to food and hair.","q3":"I can be made of saffron or indigo plants.","q4":"I‚Äôm found on some Easter eggs.","q5":"I colour things."},
"2025-03-21": {"answers":"architect,architects,engineer,engineers,civil engineer","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I make plans.","q2":"It might be good if you don‚Äôt notice my work.","q3":"I draft.","q4":"If you‚Äôre inside, you‚Äôre using my work.","q5":"I design buildings."},
"2025-03-22": {"answers":"british columbia,bc","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th: Baja California Sur.","q2":"5th: Baja California.","q3":"4th: California.","q4":"3rd: Oregon.","q5":"2nd: Washington.","message":"Sixday"},
"2025-03-23": {"answers":"mask,masks","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm worn in the ring.","q2":"I‚Äôm worn underwater.","q3":"I‚Äôm worn in the hospital.","q4":"I‚Äôm worn in a bank robbery.","q5":"I‚Äôm worn for theatre, protection, or disguise."},
"2025-03-24": {"answers":"claw,claws","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm full of muscles.","q2":"I‚Äôm your chance at a prize.","q3":"I‚Äôm similar to a wrench, chopsticks, or pliers.","q4":"I‚Äôm found on lobsters and crabs.","q5":"I‚Äôm a few-fingered grabber."},
"2025-03-25": {"answers":"cure,curing","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Some don‚Äôt have me.","q2":"I might be salty.","q3":"I‚Äôm hopefully found.","q4":"I‚Äôm a silver bullet or done to beef jerky.","q5":"I‚Äôm a culinary preservation or a medical solution.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-03-26": {"answers":"pear,pears","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm used in instrument and furniture production.","q2":"I‚Äôm lightbulb shaped.","q3":"I‚Äôm a homophone for a couple‚Äôs synonym.","q4":"You may find a partridge in my tree.","q5":"I‚Äôm a sweet fruit."},
"2025-03-27": {"answers":"hacker,hackers,hackerman","prompt":"Who am I?","q1":"I go places I‚Äôm not allowed.","q2":"I might leave no trace of where I‚Äôve been.","q3":"I might steal important information.","q4":"I might take down important systems.","q5":"I do this by typing furiously (as seen on TV)."},
"2025-03-28": {"answers":"toothpaste","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"You should see me every day.","q2":"You shouldn‚Äôt eat me.","q3":"I‚Äôm squeezed.","q4":"I‚Äôm minty.","q5":"Four out of five dentists recommend me."},
"2025-03-29": {"answers":"mount everest,everest,sagarmatha,qomolangma","prompt":"What comes first?","q1":"6th:¬†Vinson.","q2":"5th:¬†Elbrus.","q3":"4th: Kilimanjaro.","q4":"3rd:¬†Denali.","q5":"2nd: Aconcagua.","message":"Sixday"},
"2025-03-30": {"answers":"emergency","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Rules might be broken during me.","q2":"You might make a call during me.","q3":"You might need to ‚Äúdrop, cover, and hold on‚Äù in one of me...","q4":"...or you might be about to have a baby.","q5":"I‚Äôm an urgent and abnormal situation."},
"2025-03-31": {"answers":"rock,rocks","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"Eating me is an insult.","q2":"Balancing me is an art form.","q3":"Climbing me is a sport.","q4":"Having me in your shoes is an annoyance.","q5":"Crushing scissors is my winning move."},
"2025-04-01": {"answers":"sign,signs","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I show you the way.","q2":"I‚Äôm done for documents.","q3":"I‚Äôm clues for your doctor.","q4":"Your me depends on when you were born.","q5":"I‚Äôm a traffic notice, a legal acknowledgement, a medical symptom, or an astrological division.","message":"Twosday"},
"2025-04-02": {"answers":"igloo","prompt":"Where am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm warm.","q2":"I‚Äôm surrounded by cold.","q3":"I‚Äôm inside.","q4":"I‚Äôm in a dome.","q5":"I‚Äôm in a snow shelter."},
"2025-04-03": {"answers":"harp,harps","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I have strings.","q2":"I may have pedals.","q3":"I‚Äôm triangular.","q4":"I‚Äôm seen with angels and beer.","q5":"I‚Äôm a plucked string instrument."},
"2025-04-04": {"answers":"map,maps,atlas","prompt":"What am I?","q1":"I‚Äôm full of spots.","q2":"I used to be handmade.","q3":"Find yourself on me.","q4":"A local might not need me.","q5":"I‚Äôm a navigation chart."}
}